It's my life. It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a winter fire.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going.
I'm not dead.
Let's do it again, you
no gonna need you, baby.
No, I can make you my dream come true.
Don't you feel it, I
really don't know what is?
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
Three days have passed
since the battle ended.
between the Straw Hats and
the Don Quixote family.
Is Straw Hat Loopy still
hiding out in this kingdom?
Yes, that's for certain.
He's wounded.
I see.
Esau, there you are.
I heard about your spat with Sakazuki.
Glad I'm not fleet admiral anymore.
Oh, shut it. Just eat.
There's not much else for you
to do as Inspector General.
Admiral Fujitora, why haven't
you seized that pirate?
You've confirmed that he's here.
Straw Hat Luffy, the hero of Dressrosa.
Since he's a wanted man,
should I bring him in?
Or let him walk.
Because he saved this kingdom.
The decision weighs heavily on my mind.
A die.
This is no laughing matter.
That's quite enough.
Sorry.
Fool, and you, what is this?
I wonder.
If Straw Hat's an ordinary man, would
Providence spare him two days in a row?
Today's the third day, and I
haven't cheated a single time.
You, sober, now! Yes!
Coming right up, sir!
I appreciate your help with
transporting the heavenly demon,
but this island is still
under my jurisdiction.
So I'll handle things my way.
Fine by me, but the Navy can't just let
him run amok forever, not with that bounty!
Will you be down to donors?
Navy officers, please,
help us, we need you
Ah, you're back again, huh?
Yes, sir.
Well, aren't you adorable?
A dwarf they call you?
I'm Mon Cherie.
I'm from the Tintata tribe.
Aw, how cute!
Ooh, that's interesting.
Hey, what was that?
You better show some respect.
This is the daughter of
the great chief Tanta,
which means you're meeting
our princess. Now bow.
Bow before her.
Wait, Mauji. It's fine.
Oh, she's so merciful.
You see, truthfully,
our people aren't supposed
to let ourselves be seen by
anyone in Dressrosa who isn't
a member of the royal family.
So I was hoping I'd be able to heal
everyone's injuries discreetly. Really?
How's that work?
The time has come.
Yeah, I've been waiting
for this day forever.
So have I.
Take it away, Gats. We're ready.
Yes, Gats.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank
you all for being here.
Now, this day is one that
will go down in history.
Because, as you know, our
king is returning to power.
That's right.
After an entire decade, our
King Rick the Third is back!
So give it up for him, Dressrosa!
King Rick!
King Rick! King Rick!
This kingdom is mad.
That pirate fooled them,
made them hate you.
They allowed themselves to be
seduced by wealth and violence.
Only when they experienced the
fear of death did they finally
come to their senses and wish
for this land to be peaceful.
It's a farce, but I can't laugh.
Of course you can't.
Even so, I'm happy they're safe now.
Oh, I wonder if I'll be able
to make them happy as well.
Were I a god, I'd prevent any danger.
Nothing would harm them. Nothing.
What?
Now you sound like you've gone mad, hmm.
Just a thought.
We will continue our efforts after all.
What more can we do indeed?
Besides the day will come when?
when Rebecca inherits the crown.
Yes, of course.
Does that thought scare you?
You know, back when Scarlet was a young
girl, she was quite the firecracker.
What if Rebecca leaves as well?
What are you saying?
There you're all set, dear.
How lovely, a dress suits you!
Much better than that old armor of yours?
You think?
Yes!
You're beautiful lady, Rebecca.
Thank you. You know?
When you wear that dress, I swear
you look exactly like your mother!
That's true.
Oh, and we've heard
talk about your father?
too.
He was a prince from some far away land.
And rumor has it, that
prince and your mother
eloped.
After that, King Rick had no choice but
to tell everyone that Lady Scarlet was
dead.
It's like something from a romance novel.
It makes me swoon.
He was a prince? From where?
Not sure, but from the rumors I've heard,
it's a luxurious kingdom
with beautiful lakes.
Apparently, his land was at war back then.
So she and this guy ran off,
and after that, baby
Rebecca was born. Yeah?
But then, the prince
was killed in the war.
Isn't that just terrible?
So Lady Scarlet and Rebecca,
I mean, Lady Rebecca,
ended up living undercover in Dressrosa.
That's crazy.
Her dad was a prince, so her
blood's still 100 % noble.
What a bizarre rumor.
We know for certain that Sir Kiros
is the maiden's father, do we not?
I'm at a loss.
Here, have some lettuce.
This toy soldier is brave and true.
In the rain or in the snow,
he will stay with you.
All right! Huh?
They're distributing Lady
Moncheree's medicinal flowers.
They're wondrous and
proving to be very useful.
Get in line. Wait your turn.
One per person.
Thank you.
This medicine is incredible.
It heals injuries up lickety-split.
Here.
Thank you.
Look, Dad, I got you one. Thanks, son.
Let's try it out.
Wow, gone in a flash.
It's like magic.
How lucky am I?
Here, right.
Thank you so much, sir. For sure.
I see.
So you're able to use donors to
enhance your healing capability.
The power of the heal-heal
fruit really is something else.
Say, I'd be glad to donate as well.
In fact, go ahead and take enough
to patch up ten wounded people.
Wow, that's generous
of you. That's nothing.
I'll do fifteen.
You'll what?
In that case, I'll give
you enough for twenty.
Put me down for twenty-five.
Fine, then make it a hundred.
That's a bit much, but thank you all.
It's time.
I'll let you have the honor
of rolling the dice today.
If it's anything but one, then we move.
We'll go after Straw
Hat and Law immediately.
Apologies for the delay.
Indeed, they carried on and on
about Lady Rebecca's father.
I believe they were suggesting he
was a prince from some foreign land.
Yes, there it is.
Whoa, that's a strange story.
And I'm sad because Zubo's gone.
We gotta hurry and catch
up with Zubo's group, too.
You can't be hungry and angry and crying
and sleepy at the same time, Luffy.
Make up your mind.
Yeah, but that old soldier
dude is Rebecca's real dad!
You haven't fully recovered yet!
Stop stuffing your face and lie down!
Who would make up from
some crap like that?
I was the person who
got that rumor started.
Huh?
The only ones who know the truth
are some of the royal family.
and those of the Don Quixote
family who dug into my past.
The kingdom knows her mother,
but little more than that.
I spread that story before they could
find out that Rebecca is my daughter.
What?
But why?
It's because of my past.
I was a criminal.
And someone of my low breeding
could never marry royalty.
This is
better for her.
No, it isn't.
Does Rebecca know about all this stuff?
She must have read my note.
I told her the honest
truth about my whole life
because of what I did.
Rebecca suffered for a long time.
I want her to live in the light forever.
And that means she can't
have anything to do with me.
It's the only way I can make
amends for failing as her father.
When you leave this place, I'm
thinking of leaving as well.
She may resent my choice,
but she's still a child.
And I won't let her life be ruined
over a temporary fit of emotion.
King Rick understands and agrees with me.
Well, we know how Luffy feels about it.
What now?
Captain!
Uh, I mean, Sir Kuros!
It's me, Leo!
Mr. Zoro!
Mr.
Luffy, I didn't know you was awake.
What an honor.
How's your morning?
Five straw-head pirates in the same place?
And do we have mercy?
It's like a laser beam of
awesomeness is burning my eyes.
Oh, man.
If I ever saw your whole crew
of all-stars at the same time,
I don't know what I would do.
I'd probably piss myself and die.
Would you please just say
what you came here to say?
Right, sorry.
There's been some movement
over at the Navy tent.
I think they might come this way.
Vice Admiral Zuru's with them, and
the old Fleet Admiral Sengoku too.
Saru and Sengoku?
Why'd they sit in a couple
of big guns like them?
Oh no!
Sengoku.
Leo, why were you calling me?
Oh, the Navy's getting
ready to attack you!
So, it's a six, then.
This is Providence.
All troops, advance.
Find the Straw Hats and
Law, and then capture them.
Also, arrest every criminal
that's within the palace.
Let's bring all of them down!
Admiral, we can't invade.
You need clearance.
You do your job and I'll do mine.
I'll take full responsibility.
Roger.
They're on their way now.
We need to prepare quick.
Our luck has run out!
There's nothing left to prepare.
We ensured we were ready
to escape days ago.
We were waiting for Sir Luffy to awaken.
Yes, though it worked in our favor,
I must admit it was strange that
they didn't come for us earlier.
There's just one problem.
We are in need of a vessel.
That means we're dead!
We're not getting anywhere without a ship!
Hey, Leo, have you carried
out the request I made?
Yes, of course, sir.
I followed your
instructions to the letter.
Keep your distance.
It's too dangerous.
We're here to capture pirates.
Stay out of the way!
No, they'll get Lucy.
Uh-oh.
Some of the Marines are
heading up to the palace, too.
All of the fighters will need help.
Ah, thanks for your concern, little pal.
But don't worry,
we've been keeping an eye out for
the Navy ourselves this whole time.
Time to get going.
I'll lead the way.
We're gonna make a beeline
for the port in the east.
We knew you'd be ready to skip town
as soon as everybody was awake.
So our people are set up in
strategic places to help you.
They've been on standby for a while now.
They'll clear a path for you easy.
Plus, there's a ship
waiting at the eastern port.
Man, you're a lifesaver.
We let Nami's group take the Sunny,
so we were in kind of a bind.
Anything for yous guys.
We all fought together as a team.
You think we'd just roll over and
let them take our star player away?
Bellamy, can you walk?
Yeah.
Or run if I need to.
All right. Good to hear.
Trafalgar, why didn't you
leave me to my fate back there?
Thanks to you, I lost my place to die.
Straw Hat said that you were a
friend of his, so I carried you.
Die here if you want.
Now that those tiny people have patched
me up, it's like I was never injured.
So what makes you think I'm gonna be
killed off by a run-in with the damn Navy?
And find another way to die, dumbass.
What'd you say?
That's a pretty stupid
way of saying thank you.
They're here!
There's no more time for a chit-chat!
Time to start hauling some ass!
This way, comrades!
Found them!
Don't let those pirates get away!
Shoot now!
Wait, I got just the thing, period!
Don't let up, fire, I will!
Everybody follow me, alright?
We don't want to get
snapped up by Fujitora!
Stick together no matter what!
Huh? Mr. Luffy!
You guys can go on ahead.
I got something I need to do.
What?
We don't have a lot of time here, Luffy.
So whatever it is, make it quick.
We'll wait for you there.
Okay, see ya. Let's go.
Actually, you're running to the south, Mr.
Zoro.
But somehow you still
look whoops. What? Lucy?
Yes, they're about to set
sail to escape from the Navy.
Oh no, they can't.
I haven't had a chance to say thank you.
Could today be the day
his luck finally runs out?
Fate's protected him from my hand.
Until now.
From this point on, instead of
Yisho, I'm commanding all units.
And I want you to keep tracking down the
criminals who were
hidden inside the palace,
got it?
What about Straw Hat's group who were
seen running from the hill in Karta?
Just follow the flag, everybody!
Are you okay, Mr. Sniper King?
You're even cool when you fall down!
Are you sure it's safe to run straight
through the town with Marines everywhere?
Would I lie to you?
Just keep running and trust me, sir!
We're pursuing the pirates as we speak.
It looks like they're making
their way to the eastern port.
Roger that.
Get that port on the line now.
Yes, hello.
You've reached the Navy lookout unit
currently stationed at the eastern port.
Over.
Everything's good here. Over.
Everything is good.
Would it kill you to
take this more seriously?
The pirates are headed
straight towards you right now.
I don't think so.
It's all quiet on our end.
Don't bother sending backup over.
Oh yeah.
Give me your name and your marine code.
My what?
Uh, let's see, damn it all!
Oh, they've taken control
of the eastern port.
Send in some reinforcements. Sir!
Head straight to the port.
We can cover for you. Thank you!
Don't waste our time
on that thank you crap.
We owe you guys.
We'll be paying you back for a long time.
Really, a rope block?
All clear.
Wow, you're the best!
We've located the criminals who were
supposed to be at the Royal Palace,
but for some reason they're
all in the middle of town, sir!
What?
wait a second are you telling me that the
palace is empty we're in
front of the I found us!
Straw Hat's here!
Gum-Gum!
Fireworks!
Rebecca!
Hey, tell me where you are!
What is Straw Hat doing in
front of the royal palace?
Do not let him get away! Right! Rebecca!
Huh?
Hey! Huh? Rebecca!
Somebody's calling for me, but why?
Lucy? Lucy!
I'm up here!
Lucy!
No!
Don't speak to him, my lady.
He's a filthy pirate.
There you are!
Thank you. Good.
I need you to summon Viola and
Rebecca for me, please. Yes, sir.
We'll address the town.
And declare that my family and I
will be returning to the throne,
if that's what they want.
Gladly, sir.
I've been looking forward
to this day for so long.
Rebecca!
Lucy, I'm here!
Thank goodness!
Strata, what do you want?
Please get back, Lady Rebecca.
What a relief!
You're still here!
Listen, I wanted to say thank you for...
Shut up!
That's not the reason why I came!
Are you okay with all of this? Huh?
Soldier, I mean!
He's gonna leave forever!
Well, the thing is, he sent me a letter.
It sounds like he's trying to put as much
distance between him and me as possible.
He wants us to be strangers from now on.
Oh, shut up!
Stop acting like you're my father!
It must be because of the
terrible things I said to him.
You can't beat the flamingo!
Look at yourself!
You're just a broken toy with one leg!
Do you think he doesn't
want us to live together?
Maybe I'm just a nuisance.
Beats me, not my call!
I just came to ask if you're
fine with him leaving!
So tell me, cause I gotta
get out of this kingdom too!
Of course not!
It's not okay at all!
Then come with me!
Let's go.
Lady Rebecca!
Hold on, Straw Hat, Rebecca!
Viola!
I need a favor from you!
Taking off!
Hey, don't let go! I'm trying!
There he is!
Your Majesty!
What's the matter?
It's terrible.
Lady Rebecca's been
carried away by a pirate!
A pirate?
What was his name?
Where did he come from?
Tell me everything!
Was he a warrior from the Coliseum?
Um, it...
It was...
It was Straw Hat Luffy, sir!
A man just came to the palace
and kidnapped Lady Rebecca!
I'm pretty sure it was Straw
Hat Luffy, right? I think so.
He's probably taking her
for ransom, isn't he?
But that can't be.
Lucy, it doesn't sound like him at all.
I'm sure there's a reason.
Hey, Lucy!
I still love you!
What are you saying? You see?
This is what happens when you
trust pirates to do as they please.
Now go capture Straw Hat and return
the princess to the palace safely.
Up there!
Special sniper unit,
take your shot, quickly!
Oh no, they collapsed out of nowhere!
It knocked them down, conquerors Haki!
No, looks like they're
still conscious regardless.
The pirates are about to escape!
I want battle ships in place.
Send all of our forces east to Korta, sir
There he is
What's going on?
Lucy!
That's my dinner! I'm sorry!
Listen.
I'm gonna drop you off at the hill.
I'll lure them away.
Can you run for it, okay?
Seems like everybody's
on the lookout for you.
If you get caught, they'll
take you back to the palace.
Red, got it.
We better hurry, though.
I don't know how long you'll stay.
Thank you for everything
you've done, Lucy.
No problem.
Glad it worked out.
My little girl.
You're so cute.
Stop crying.
Scarlet.
I fulfilled my duty.
Forgive me for cooking up
a lie about our marriage.
I just want Rebecca to live a happy life.
Safe from my past.
You're going to learn to defend yourself.
Mother said I shouldn't
hurt others no matter what.
But you must protect yourself
from those who would hurt you.
Stand up, child.
Don't give up.
Because you're a member
of the royal family,
you've had to endure the hatred of
this nation for an entire decade.
But this time, it will be different.
You can live the life
you were meant to lead,
a peaceful one.
But that's not a world
that I can be a part of.
Rebecca!
How dare you lie to me?
Oh, the letter.
I wasn't lying.
Look, I have a terrible history.
I was a sorry excuse for a man
always getting into fights.
And I was a killer, too.
I can't deny what I've done.
That's the honest truth.
All right, but why did you say I
was the daughter of some prince?
That's such a hateful lie.
It doesn't matter how many
people he may have killed,
or how much his hands
are tainted in blood.
I only have one father.
I'm proud to say I'm
the daughter of Kiros.
So you don't have to lie.
Happiness will return to you.
Till then, I'll stay by your side.
I want you to stay with me.
You promised, soldier.
Even after all the things that I've done.
Let's live together.
Okay, Dad.
Sorry, father, but it seems
Rebecca won't be coming back.
Very well.
I thought as much.
I'm glad.
She made her own decision.
Viola, I'm sorry, but
please take my place.
I'm sorry, Viola.
Please take my place.
You mean as princess?
I can't believe I've had to
grant such a request twice.
Rebecca really is just
like her mother, isn't she?
Luffy isn't here yet?
I haven't seen Law anywhere either.
They're the ones who are
supposed to be running this show.
Our group is pretty tough, but what
if the Navy brings out the big guns?
Here he comes.
FUCHI Dorry!
Idiot, we're dead.
Hurry up, Mr. Luffy!
What now? Huh?
Only one option.